[{"answer": "Well, they have started the debate on the procedural issues, but I just actually am getting an e-mail right now saying that the final vote, it doesn't look like it will happen until much later, until some time between 11:15 and 11:45 Eastern.", "docId": "130101pmt", "aSentId": 17, "question": "Dana, I take it they started the actual debate, the vote could be fairly soon?", "qSentId": 16}, {"answer": "He's never been officially wedded to that majority of the majority idea.", "docId": "130101pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "If the majority is not there of the Republicans who are the majority in the House, he's not going to bring it up for a vote, or are they discarding that given this current crisis?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "They're not saying that, but he is -- he is here in the building, and this would be a victory.", "docId": "130101pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "So there's a possibility that he might actually go before cameras and make a statement assuming it passes the House?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "They are still there.", "docId": "130101pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "I take it there's no full lid, as they say, over in the West Wing at the White House, meaning that there's still a possibility that the TV crew are still there?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Hi, Wolf.", "docId": "130101pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "Congresswoman, you're going to vote which way for this Senate bill?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "I'm a very reluctant yes, Wolf, because under these circumstances which exist, this last-minute situation exists because the folks just back behind me in the Senate chamber, Senator Reid, could not get the Senate to act on any of the great bills for the American people we sent before, this is the best we can do given the Senate and the White House sentiment at this point in time.", "docId": "130101pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "Are you going to vote in favor of the Senate bill or are you going to vote against it?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "I think that's probably a valid assumption, Wolf.", "docId": "130101pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "Is that a correct assumption?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "That's what I anticipate, Wolf, and I certainly will be glad to get this particular issue settled and now it's on to tackling that hideous problem that we have and we owe it to the American people to do everything we can.", "docId": "130101pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "And so you assume like I do that it will pass the House of Representatives, a bipartisan majority, more than 217 votes and it will go to the president for his signature perhaps as early as tomorrow?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's hard to say.", "docId": "130101pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "LITZER: How many Democrats -- how many Democrats do you think will vote in favor of this Senate-passed version?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "Well, I'm pretty confident that the legislation is going to pass, what I'm hopeful is, really, actually anyone watching this, Wolf, should have just taken out some stock in Dramamine because the rollercoaster ride that has resulted from us getting to this process really has been unfortunate and unnecessary but we're here.", "docId": "130101pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "Do you have any doubt that this legislation will be passed tonight?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "Well, I'm a progressive.", "docId": "130101pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "What do you say to those colleagues of yours who don't like this deal?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130101pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "But you agree, Grover, with Debbie Wasserman Schultz, if you were a member of the House or the Senate, you'd be voting for this legislation as well?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "They're not -- they're not voting for a tax increase, they're voting to save tax cuts for as many people as they can over Obama's objections.", "docId": "130101pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "But -- I just want to make sure -- I just want to point out, Grover Norquist, though, having said all that and everything you said, you are giving cover to those Republicans who will vote in favor of the Senate legislation in the next hour or two?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "Oh, I'm going to vote for it.", "docId": "130101pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "Yes, I assume you're in favor of this Senate-passed language?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Well, I'm interested in seeing how many votes the Republicans are going to provide.", "docId": "130101pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "Is that the number you're hearing?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "I'm talking about Tea Party Republicans who continue to throw temper tantrums and delay this and refuse to move forward in the spirit of compromise.", "docId": "130101pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "You say children, you're talking about the Speaker of the House and the Majority Leader?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "Oh, I think a good part of this has had nothing to do with an economic strategy.", "docId": "130101pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "You think the Republican leadership, the speaker, the majority leader, some of the other leaders, they're all on the same page or are they fighting amongst themselves?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "Well, I wasn't completely surprised because there are a lot of Democrats particularly in the Senate, particularly representing wealthy states like New York, Chuck Schumer, for example, who always kind of wanted that threshold to go up a bit.", "docId": "130101pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "Were you surprised the president was willing to go up to $450,000 from $250,000, which he had spoken of for months and months and months during the campaign?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "Well, I guess it depends on for who.", "docId": "130101pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "God deal or bad deal?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "I think President Obama played a much stronger hand and won with it in this sort of shoving match over -- particularly forcing Republicans to go ahead and raise taxes on the rich.", "docId": "130101pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "Who is the big political winner tonight, Ben?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "I think he was just overheard on the floor of the House calling tonight a nightmare for him.", "docId": "130101pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "Assuming it passes, Ben Smith, what do you think the future for John Boehner, the speaker, is?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "We just got a little bit of good news that it might happen in the 10:00 hour, a little bit earlier.", "docId": "130101pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "Around 11:00, 11:15, that's when roll call will take place?", "qSentId": 476}]